newsle.com 2015-07-11

# newsle: privacy policy

**Last Updated: November 25, 2013**

This Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Newsle and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies ("Newsle" or "We"). This privacy policy ("Policy") applies to the websites of Newsle, including Newsle.com, and Newsle’s online services (collectively, "Services"). This Policy does not apply to websites, applications or services that display or link to different privacy statements.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect information about you in various ways when you use our Services. We collect personal information you provide to us. For example, we collect your name, email address, demographics, photos and other information you provide us through our Services. If you choose to connect your social networking and email accounts to our Service, we may collect your profile data, your photo, the email address you use for those accounts, and your list of connections, including their profile data and photos, and contact information. We also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. Because of the nature of our Services we also collect and compile publicly available information about persons that our users follow or may wish to follow, including, for example, news articles, blog posts and public profiles, names and photos.

When you visit our website, some information is automatically collected, for example, we collect information about your computer's operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and the website you visited before our site are logged automatically. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Services. 

**Cookies.** We may automatically collect information using "cookies." Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Services and your experience. We use cookies to understand usage, to see which areas and features are popular, and to count visits to our website. We also use cookies to remember your website preferences. 

**Web Beacons.** We may collect information using Web beacons. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Services or in our emails. We use Web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

Other parties may collect information including personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our Services, some of those activities are described in this Policy.

**ADVERTISING**

We may use third parties to serve ads on our Services. Certain third parties may automatically collect information about your visits to this and other websites, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you use to visit our Site (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number). They do this using cookies, clear gifs or other technologies. Information collected may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other sites tracked by these third parties. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear gifs in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: http://www.networkadvertising.org.

**USE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We use personal information collected through our Services for purposes described in this Policy or disclosed to you on our Services or in connection with our services. For example, we may use your information and contacts you choose to upload to Newsle to:

  * create your private and public profile and use your public profile and information including your name, photo, blog posts, and news articles about you to display and send to others, including those who follow you or who we think may wish to follow you; 
  * for commercial purposes using your name, picture, image, and/or likeness including to let other people, such as your friends, connections, and contacts, know that you are a registered user of Newsle and that you have taken particular action(s) on the Service;
  * operate and improve our Services;
  * understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our Services;
  * respond to your comments and questions and provide customer service;

  * provide and deliver services and information you request;
  * send you information relating to your account, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;

  * email you with news about people you are following, people you may wish to follow, upcoming events, and other news about products and services offered by Newsle and our selected partners;
  * send emails on your behalf to friends and connections you would like to invite to use our service using email addresses in your contacts and email addresses of other users who share common contacts with you and to send email invites for other users who share contacts in common with you using the email addresses of contacts that you uploaded (we never show other users the email addresses of your contacts unless, of course, they already have those);
  * solicit your feedback about our services;
  * link or combine your information with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and 
  * protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity.

Newsle will store and process personal information in the United States and other countries that may have data protection protections that differ from your home country. 

**SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Information You Share**

Our Services allow you to connect and share information such as your name, profile, photos, actions, comments, content, and other information publicly and with other people. You may also connect to, and share your information on, third party websites and services through our Service. Please be mindful of your own privacy needs as you choose who to connect with and what to share and make public. We cannot control the privacy or security of information you choose to make public or share with others. We are also not responsible for the privacy practices of thrid party websites and services.

**Information We Share**

Because of the nature of our Services we share publicly available information about persons that our users follow or may wish to follow, including, for example, news articles, blog posts, names and photos. We do not share non-public personal information you give us with third parties other than as described in this Policy and as follows:

  * with your consent, for example, when you agree to our sharing your information with other third parties for their own marketing purposes subject to their separate privacy policies;
  * with third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who work for us and need access to your information to do that work;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect the rights and property of Newsle our agents, customers, and others including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms of use or (iii) in an emergency to protect the personal safety of Newsle, its customers, or any person;
  * in connection with or during negotiation of any merger, financing, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, transaction or proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture or disclosure of all or a portion of our business or assets to another company.

We may also share aggregated or deidentified information.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Newsle takes reasonable steps to help protect your non-public personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. 

**YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES**

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Newsle by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. You may also send requests about your contact preferences, changes to your information including requests to opt-out of sharing your non-public personal information with third parties by [contacting us](https://help.linkedin.com/app/ask/path/ppq/). 

Subject to applicable law, you may delete your account by going to newsle.com/settings and selecting "Delete My Account" at the bottom of the settings dialog. You may also request deletion of information and content you post about yourself by contacting Newsle and verifying your identity.    Newsle does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information posted on our Site by registered account holders, further deletion of your account will not affect information, content, and news posted about you by others or information, content, and news posted about you and reposted by Newsle.

You can revoke or modify Newsle’s permissions to access social networking accounts you have connected with Newsle by using the privacy settings for those respective services.

Third party service providers, such as analytics service providers, who act on our behalf may track individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services and may or may not honor any or all Web browser "do not track" signals and other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice. To learn more about some of the analytics service providers we use and choices they may give you about tracking please visit their privacy policies: KISSmetrics ([KISSmetrics Privacy Policy](https://www.kissmetrics.com/) and [Opt-Out](https://www.kissmetrics.com/user-privacy)), Optimizely (https://www.optimizely.com/privacy), and GoogleAnalytics ([Google Analytics Privacy](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and Google Analytics [Opt-Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) Browser Add-On). Please note that this is not an exhaustive list and we may change these from time to time.

Many web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove and reject cookies we set directly from Newsle.com servers. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Site.  

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**  

Newsle may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. 

**QUESTIONS**

If you have any questions about this Policy, please [contact us](https://help.linkedin.com/app/ask/path/ppq/).
